

# **Harry Johnson**

Product Engineer at Eigen Technologies



harry ]dot[ johnson500 ]at[ `gmail` ]dot[ com
[CV]

### **About**

Experienced Software and Product Engineer currently working at AI scale-up Eigen Technologies . Co-leader of the MLOps team, we build data and compute pipelines to productionise research models for unstructured-data extraction.

I learned Domain Driven Design (DDD) coding against a large in-house ERP system in PHP, my background is in Python for data analytics and process automation, and I have experience managing software implementation projects in an enterprise environment.

In my spare time, I am learning Rust and practicing Data Science, with an interest in parallel processing.

### **Experience**

Product Engineer

Eigen Technologies: 2021 - present

**Co-Leading the ML-Infrastructure team:** I am responsible for working with Data Science, Product Management, and the ML-Infrastructure team to productionise our machine learning capabilities. I manage the migration of our legacy embedded ML infrastructure to a Kubernetes-first microservice configuration, as well as the implementation of new features. I lead design sessions, co-ordinate with stakeholders, manage timelines, and contribute to implementation. I prioritise scalability, modularity, extensibility, and lowering the long-term maintenance burden with rigorous attention to software interfaces and data contracts.

**Before co-leading ML-Infrastructure:** Contributed to design and implementation of a microservice-oriented DDD refactoring of critical project models, collaborated developing an async client for remote system testing, tools for system observability on client deployments, and various reporting features.

- AWS (EC2, S3, ELK)
- Azure
- Dagster
- MLFlow
- BentoML
- Kubernetes
- o Helm
- Docker (+Compose)
- Pvthon 3
- PostgreSQL
- Redis
- Celerv
- Microservice Architecture
- React

#### Software Engineer

Gigabyte Software: 2018 - 2021

Full-stack development - I was responsible for liaising with clients to collate requirements, designing and implementing new functionality in our proprietary ERP system, while also maintaining the existing codebase. On occasion, I was responsible for resolving infrastructure issues. I managed and worked on the Barclays Bank integration project, liaising with Barclays and our client, and planning and executing the design-implementation-test cycle. I designed and implemented (with the team) a supplier management module, and a postal mail integration with ClickSend, among others.

- o PHP (5.6, 7.4), Symfony, Doctrine,
- MySQL
- o Ubuntu Server
- Redis
- Beanstalk
- o DDD
- React (+Redux, +Saga)
- Heroku
- o AWS S3
- AWS CloudFront

#### Competitive Intelligence Analyst, Product Strategy

Finastra, London: 2016 - 2018

I managed the implementation of a 3rd party innovation application, and designed and managed the implementation of a custom post-deal survey component in the company Salesforce instance. I used pandas and the PyData stack to produce quarterly reports for the C-Level. I built a Flask web application to hold my current work-state, and generate reports for my manager. I used the Python web-scraping tools to collect data on competitors, and pandas and PyData to combine it with deal information to produce heatmaps for regional sales targeting.

- Python (2, 3)
- Flask
- o pandas, numpy, Plotly, Bokeh
- o pptx
- Salesforce API

#### Business Intelligence Analyst, Sales Operations

Misys (now Finastra), London: 2014 - 2016

Working in Sales Operations, I identified multiple manual processes available for automation. I automated various operational and reporting processes I was tasked with, including the Global Deal Review, using the Python Win32COM APIs, MS Office Python packages, Salesforce integration, pandas, and a variety of visualisation tools.

- Python (2)
- o pandas, numpy, Plotly
- Salesforce API
- o pywin32
- [Please see my LinkedIn ☐ for further employment history]

## **Expertise in Technologies and Methodologies**

- Domain Driven Design
- Software and Data Architecture
- Agile
- Microservice Architecture
- Python
  - Dagster

- o BentoML
- SKLearn
- HuggingFace
- Django
- Flask
- Pandas (+ PyData ecosystem)
- Wagtail CMS
- Django Rest Framework
- Scrapy (BeautifulSoup, Pattern, nltk)
- Celery

#### Devops

- Docker
- Vagrant
- Ansible
- Kubernetes

#### Cloud Providers

- AWS
- Azure

#### • SQL

- MySQL
- o PostgreSQL

#### • NoSQL

MongoDB

#### • PHP

- Symfony
- Doctrine

#### Javascript

- VanillaJS
- o ES6
- React (+Redux, +Saga)

#### • Linux Server Administration

- Bash/Shell Scripting
- Apache Web Server
- Logging

## **Education**

• University of Edinburgh

2009 - 2013

• Mander Portman Woodward College

2007 - 2008

• Eton College

2003 - 2007